Guide to the Montana State College, Office of the President Annual Reports Received 1921-1968
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
- Graduate Studies, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/22)
- Graduate Studies, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/23)
- Graduate Studies, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 4/24)
- Graduate Studies, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/25)
- Graduate Studies, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/26)
- Graduate Studies, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/27)
- Graduate Studies, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/28)
- Graduate Studies, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/29)
- Graduate Studies, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4/30)
- Graduate Studies, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 4/31)
- Graduate Studies, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4/32)
- Graphics and Duplicating, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/33)
- Graphics and Duplicating, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/34)
- Hannon Hall, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/35)
- Hannon Hall, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/36)
- Hannon Hall, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/37)
- Health and Physical Education, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/38)
- Health and Physical Education, 1923/1924-1928/1929 (Box-folder 4/39)
- Health and Physical Education, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4/40)
- Health and Physical Education, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4/41)
- Health and Physical Education, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4/42)
- Health and Physical Education, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/43)
- Health and Physical Education, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/44)
- Health and Physical Education, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4/45)
- Health and Physical Education, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/46)
- Health and Physical Education, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/47)
- Health and Physical Education, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/48)
- Health and Physical Education, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/49)
- Health and Physical Education, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/50)
- Health and Physical Education, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/51)
- Health and Physical Education, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/52)
- Health and Physical Education, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/53)
- Health and Physical Education, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 4/54)
- Health and Physical Education, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/55)
- Health and Physical Education, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/56)
- Health and Physical Education, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 4/57)
- Health and Physical Education, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4/58)
- Health and Physical Education, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4/59)
- Health and Physical Education, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/60)
- Health and Physical Education, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/61)
- Health and Physical Education, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/62)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/63)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/64)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4/65)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/66)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/67)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/68)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1957 (Box-folder 4/69)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/70)
- Health and Physical Education Women, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/71)
- Health Committee, 1929-1937 (Box-folder 4/72)
- Health Committee, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 4/73)
- Health Committee, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4/74)
- Health Committee, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4/75)
- Health Committee, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4/76)
- Health Committee, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/77)
- Health Committee, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/78)
- Health Committee, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/79)
- Health Committee, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/80)
- Health Committee, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/81)
- Health Committee, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/82)
- Health Committee, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/83)
- Health Committee, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/84)
- Health Committee, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/85)
- Health Committee, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/86)
- Health Committee, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/87)
- Health Committee, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/88)
- Health Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/89)
- Histories: 75th Anniversary Letters and Science, 1893-1967 (Box-folder 4/90)
- Histories: 75th Anniversary Government and Philosophy, 1893-1967 (Box-folder 4/91)
- History, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/92)
- History, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 4/93)
- History, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/94)
- History, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/95)
- History, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/96)
- History, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/97)
- History, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/98)
- History, 1928/11929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 4/99)
- History, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4/100)
- History, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4/101)
- History, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4/102)
- History, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/103)
- History, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/104)
- History, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4/105)
- History, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/106)
- History, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/107)
- History, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/108)
- History, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/109)
- History, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/110)
- History, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/111)
- History, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/112)
- History, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/113)
- History, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/114)
- History Experiment Station/Branch Station (Box-folder 4/115)
- Home Economics, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4/116)
- Home Economics, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4/117)
- Home Economics, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4/118)
- Home Economics, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/119)
- Home Economics, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/120)
- Home Economics, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4/121)
- Home Economics, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/122)
- Home Economics, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/123)
- Home Economics, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/124)
- Home Economics, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/125)
- Home Economics, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/126)
- Home Economics, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/127)
- Home Economics, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/128)
- Home Economics, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/129)
- Home Economics, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/130)
- Home Economics, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/131)
- Home Economics, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 4/132)
- Home Economics, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/133)
- Home Economics, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/134)
- Home Economics, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/135)
- Home Economics, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/136)
- Home Economics, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 4/137)
- Home Economics, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4/138)
- Horticulture, 1928/1929-1937 (Box-folder 4/139)
- Horticulture, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4/140)
- Horticulture, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4/141)
- Horticulture, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/142)
- Horticulture, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/143)
- Horticulture, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4/144)
- Horticulture, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/145)
- Horticulture, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/146)
- Horticulture, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/147)
- Horticulture, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/148)
- Horticulture, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/149)
- Horticulture, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/150)
- Horticulture, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/151)
- Horticulture, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 4/152)
- Horticulture, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/153)
- Horticulture, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/154)
- Horticulture, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 4/155)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 4/156-157)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4/158)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4/159)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4/160)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4/161)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4/162)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4/163)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/164)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/165)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/166)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/167)
- Household and Industrial Arts, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/168)
- Housing, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/169)
- Housing Director, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/170)
- Housing: Single and Married Men's, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/171)
- Housing: Single and Married Men's, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/172)
- Industrial Arts, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/173)
- Industrial Arts, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/174)
- Industrial Arts, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/175)
- Industrial Arts, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/176)
- Industrial Arts, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/177)
- Industrial Arts, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/178)
- Industrial Arts, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/179)
- Industrial Arts, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/180)
- Industrial Arts, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/181)
- Industrial Arts, 1961 (Box-folder 4/182)
- Industrial Arts, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4/183)
- Industrial Arts (Box-folder 4/184)
- Information, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/185)
- Information, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4/186)
- Information, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/187)
- Information, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 4/188)
- Information, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4/189)
- International Education Exchange Program, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/190)
- International Education Exchange Program, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/191)
- International Education Exchange Program, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 4/192)
- Intramural Athletics, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/193)
- Intramural Athletics, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/194)
- Librarian, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 5/1)
- Librarian, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 5/2)
- Librarian, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 5/3)
- Librarian, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/4)
- Librarian, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/5)
- Librarian, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/6)
- Librarian, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/7)
- Librarian, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/8)
- Librarian, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/9)
- Librarian, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/10)
- Librarian, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/11)
- Librarian, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/12)
- Librarian, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5/13)
- Librarian, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/14)
- Librarian, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/15)
- Librarian, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/16)
- Librarian, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/17)
- Librarian, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/18)
- Librarian, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/19)
- Librarian, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/20)
- Librarian, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/21)
- Librarian, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5/22)
- Librarian, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 5/23)
- Librarian, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 5/24)
- Librarian, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 5/25)
- Librarian, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 5/26)
- Librarian, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 5/27)
- Mathematics, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 5/28)
- Mathematics, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 5/29)
- Mathematics, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 5/30)
- Mathematics, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/31)
- Mathematics, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/32)
- Mathematics, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/33)
- Mathematics, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/34)
- Mathematics, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/35)
- Mathematics, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/36)
- Mathematics, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/37)
- Mathematics, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/38)
- Mathematics, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/39)
- Mathematics, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5/40)
- Mathematics, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/41)
- Mathematics, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/42)
- Mathematics, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/43)
- Mathematics, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/44)
- Mathematics, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/45)
- Mathematics, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/46)
- Mathematics, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/47)
- Mathematics, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/48)
- Mathematics, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5/49)
- Mathematics, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 5/50)
- Loan Fund Committee, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/51)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1928/1929-1935/1936 (Box-folder 5/52)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 5/53)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 5/54)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/55)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/56)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/57)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/58)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/59)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/60)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/61)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/62)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5/63)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1949/1950 (Box-folder 5/64)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/65)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/66)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/67)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/68)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/69)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/70)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5/71)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 5/72)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 5/73)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 5/74)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 5/75)
- Men's Housing, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/76)
- Men's Housing, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/77)
- Military Science, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 5/78)
- Military Science, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 5/79)
- Military Science, 1931-1937 (Box-folder 5/80)
- Military Science, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/81)
- Military Science, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/82)
- Military Science, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/83)
- Military Science, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/84)
- Military Science, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/85)
- Military Science, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/86)
- Military Science, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/87)
- Military Science, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/88)
- Military Science, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/89)
- Military Science, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5/90)
- Military Science, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/91)
- Military Science, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/92)
- Military Science, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/93)
- Military Science, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/94)
- Military Science, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/95)
- Military Science, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/96)
- Military Science, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/97)
- Military Science, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/98)
- Modern Language, 1929/1930-1936/1937 (Box-folder 5/99)
- Modern Language, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 5/100)
- Modern Language, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 5/101)
- Modern Language, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/102)
- Modern Language, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/103)
- Modern Language, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/104)
- Modern Language, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/105)
- Modern Language, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/106)
- Modern Language, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/107)
- Modern Language, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/108)
- Modern Language, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/109)
- Modern Language, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/110)
- Modern Language, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5/111)
- Modern Language, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/112)
- Modern Language, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/113)
- Modern Language, 1952 (Box-folder 5/114)
- Modern Language, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/115)
- Modern Language, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/116)
- Modern Language, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/117)
- Modern Language, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/118)
- Modern Language, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/119)
- Modern Language, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5/120)
- Modern Language, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 5/121)
- Modern Language, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 5/122)
- Music, 1929/1930-1936/1937 (Box-folder 5/123)
- Music, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 5/124)
- Music, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 5/125)
- Music, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/126)
- Music, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/127)
- Music, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/128)
- Music, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/129)
- Music, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/130)
- Music, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/131)
- Music, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/132)
- Music, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/133)
- Music, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/134)
- Music, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5/135)
- Music, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/136)
- Music, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/137)
- Music, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/138)
- Music, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/139)
- Music, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/140)
- Music, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/141)
- Music, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/142)
- Music, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5/143)
- Music, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 5/144)
- Music, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 5/145)
- ROTC History (Box-folder 5/146)
- Nursing, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 5/147)
- Nursing, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 5/148)
- Nursing, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 5/149)
- Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 5/150)
- Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5/151)
- Nursing, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/152)
- Nursing, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 5/153)
- Nursing, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/154)
- Nursing, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 5/155)
- Nursing, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 5/156)
- Nursing, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 5/157)
- Nursing, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/158)
- Nursing, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/159)
- Nursing, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5/160)
- Nursing, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/161)
- Nursing Orientation Manual for Nurse Instructors (Box-folder 5/162)
- Nursing, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 5/163)
- Nursing, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5/164)
- Nursing, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/165)
- Nursing, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/166)
- Nursing, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/167)
- Nursing, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/168)
- Nursing, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 5/169)
- Nursing, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 5/170)
- Nursing: Deaconess Bozeman Unit, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/171)
- Nursing: Deaconess Great Falls Unit, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 5/172)
- Personnel Committee, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6/1)
- Physical Education 75th History, 1924-1967 (Box-folder 6/2)
- Physical Education Men 50th History, 1943 (Box-folder 6/3)
- Physical Education Women 50th History, 1943 (Box-folder 6/4)
- Physical Plant (Box-folder 6/5)
- Physical Plant, 1929-1937 (Box-folder 6/6)
- Physical Plant, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 6/7)
- Physical Plant, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 6/8)
- Physical Plant, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 6/9)
- Physical Plant, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 6/10)
- Physical Plant, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 6/11)
- Physical Plant, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 6/12)
- Physical Plant, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6/13)
- Physical Plant, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6/14)
- Physical Plant, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 6/15)
- Physical Plant, 1963 (Box-folder 6/16)
- Physics, 1929/1930-1936/1937 (Box-folder 6/17)
- Physics, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 6/18)
- Physics, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 6/19)
- Physics, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 6/20)
- Physics, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 6/21)
- Physics, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 6/22)
- Physics, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 6/23)
- Physics, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 6/24)
- Physics, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 6/25)
- Physics, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6/26)
- Physics, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6/27)
- Physics, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 6/28)
- Physics, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 6/29)
- Physics, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 6/30)
- Physics, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 6/31)
- Physics, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 6/32)
- Physics, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 6/33)
- Physics, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6/34)
- Physics, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6/35)
- Physics, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 6/36)
- Physics, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/37)
- Physics, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6/38)
- Physics, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 6/39)
- Physics, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 6/40)
- Physics, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 6/41)
- Placement Office, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 6/42)
- Placement Office, 1952 (Box-folder 6/43)
- Placement Office, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6/44)
- Placement Office, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6/45)
- Placement Office, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 6/46)
- Placement Office, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/47)
- Placement Office, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6/48)
- Placement Office, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 6/49)
- Placement Office, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 6/50)
- Placement Office, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 6/51)
- Placement Office, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 6/52)
- Placement Office, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 6/53)
- Plant and Soil Science, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 6/54)
- Plant and Soil Science, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 6/55)
- Plant and Soil Science, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 6/56)
- Poultry Industry, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6/57)
- Poultry Industry, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6/58)
- Poultry Industry, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 6/59)
- Poultry Industry, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 6/60)
- Poultry Industry, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 6/61)
- Poultry Industry, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6/62)
- Poultry Industry, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 6/63)
- Poultry Industry, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/64)
- Poultry Industry, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 6/65)
- Pre Medical, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 6/66)
- Pre Medical, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 6/67)
- Pre Medical, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 6/68)
- Pre Medical, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 6/69)
- Pre Medical, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 6/70)
- Professional Schools, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 6/71)
- Psychology, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/72)
- Psychology, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6/73)
- Psychology, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 6/74)
- Psychology, 1962 (Box-folder 6/75)
- Pubic Service, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6/76)
- Pubic Service, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 6/77)
- Pubic Service, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 6/78)
- Pubic Service, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 6/79)
- Pubic Service, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 6/80)
- Pubic Service, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6/81)
- Pubic Service, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6/82)
- Pubic Service, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 6/83)
- Pubic Service, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/84)
- Pubic Service, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6/85)
- Pubic Service, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 6/86)
- Pubic Service, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 6/87)
- Pubic Service, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 6/88)
- Pubic Service, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 6/89)
- Publications, 1930-1937 (Box-folder 6/90)
- Publications, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 6/91)
- Publications, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 6/92)
- Publications, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 6/93)
- Publications, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 6/94)
- Publications, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 6/95)
- Publications, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 6/96)
- Publications, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 6/97)
- Publications, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 6/98)
- Publications, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6/99)
- Publications, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6/100)
- Publications, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 6/101)
- Publications, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 6/102)
- Publications, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 6/103)
- Publications, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 6/104)
- Publications, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 6/105)
- Publications, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6/106)
- Publications, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6/107)
- Publications, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 6/108)
- Publications, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/109)
- Publications, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6/110)
- Registrar, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 6/111)
- Registrar, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 6/112)
- Registrar, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 6/113)
- Registrar, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 6/114)
- Registrar, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 6/115)
- Registrar, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 6/116)
- Research Foundation, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 7/1)
- Rural Engineering, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 7/2)
- Rural Engineering, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 7/3)
- Rural Engineering, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 7/4)
- Rural Engineering, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 7/5)
- Rural Engineering, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 7/6)
- Rural Engineering, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7/7)
- Rural Engineering, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7/8)
- Rural Engineering, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 7/9)
- Science, 1931/1932-1933/1934 (Box-folder 7/10)
- Science, 1934/1935-3196/1937 (Box-folder 7/11)
- Science, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 7/12)
- Science, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 7/13)
- Science, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 7/14)
- Science, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 7/15)
- Science, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 7/16)
- Science, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 7/17)
- Science, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 7/18)
- Science, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 7/19)
- Science, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7/20)
- Science, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7/21)
- Science, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 7/22)
- Science, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 7/23)
- Science, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 7/24)
- Science, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 7/25)
- Science, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 7/26)
- Science, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 7/27)
- Science, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 7/28)
- Science, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 7/29)
- Science, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 7/30)
- Science, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 7/31)
- Science, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 7/32)
- Science, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 7/33)
- Science: Entomology, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 7/34)
- Science: Entomology, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 7/35)
- Science: Entomology, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 7/36)
- Science: Entomology, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 7/37)
- Science: Entomology, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 7/38)
- Science: Zoology, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 7/39)
- Science: Zoology, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 7/40)
- Science: Zoology, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 7/41)
- Science: Zoology, 1928/1929-1934/1935 (Box-folder 7/42)
- Science: Zoology, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 7/43)
- Science: Zoology, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 7/44)
- Science: Zoology, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 7/45)
- Science: Zoology, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 7/46)